are constantly fed a steady stream of programming that makes us believe that things only have two
sides. No, Israel does not have America by the nuts. America and Israel, they are both held
by the same people. Okay. So when people say like, it's chestnut checkers, right? Or,
you know, they frame things in a game mindset that already lets you know the limitations
of their comprehension because they are looking at things as if there are only two sides.
Okay. They are looking at things as if they are oppositional. And that is a way that we have been
trained. Look at these two sports teams. They're oppositional. You know, we look at things like
the NFL and the NBA and, you know, other, other sports and people are obsessed with their sports
teams as if this person who was on this team cannot be traded to now be on this team. Now
they are presented to you as oppositional. However, they're all ruled by the same hands.
These owners don't give a damn about the individuals. They are solely in the business
of making money for the corporation. The owners of the teams form the NFL. The teams, the boys,
the brothers, they don't form the NFL. The owners do. So the decisions they're making about their teams
is for the purpose of upholding the NFL. But you're down here on the bottom fighting over this team
versus that team. The same way that we are here in the United States fighting over Democrats versus
Republicans. When no, Democrats and Republicans are ruled by the same overarching hand. So is Israel
and the United States. They are not oppositional. They are ruled by the same hand. We are fed a steady
stream of good guy, bad guy, right? We're fed a steady stream of David Goliath. No, no, it's not that
basic. Someone in here just said, Jay-Z is the director of music for the NFL. So things are getting
better. Man, are y'all, you, you can't be that dumb. I'm calling you dumb.